# **Chimera Collins**

## Cashier/Sale Associate

Philadelphia, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Chimera-Collins/fb8442e65a8c724d

Friendly and energetic with 2 years in the childcare industry. Motivated to help children become happy, healthy and well-behaved. Reliable Child Care Worker talented at creating a safe, stimulating environment for young children. Expertly leads individual and group activities to encourage learning and develop social interaction skills. Approachable Daycare Provider successful at making children and parents feel at ease. Strengths include conflict resolution and special needs childcare services.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## Cashier/Sale Associate

Wal-Mart - King of Prussia, PA - November 2015 to January 2016

#### Seasonal

- \* •Documented all customer inquiries and comments thoroughly and guickly.
- \* •Processed cash and credit payments rapidly and accurately.
- \* •Responded to all customer inquiries thoroughly and professionally.
- \* •Placed special merchandise orders for customers.
- \* •Greeted customers in a timely fashion, while quickly determining their needs.
- \* •Answered customer questions about product availability and shipment times.

# Housekeeping

Wyndham Hotel - Philadelphia, PA - March 2014 to October 2015

- \* •Greeted and welcomed all hotel guests with a smile.
- \* •Escorted guests to their assigned rooms, including transporting their luggage.
- \* •Resolved service-related problems in a timely manner.
- \* •Solicited feedback through questionnaires to evaluate levels of guest satisfaction.
- \* •Vacuumed rugs and carpeted areas in offices, lobbies and corridors.
- \* •Removed waste paper and other trash from the premises to designated area.
- \* •Changed bed linens and collected soiled linens for cleaning.
- \* •Disinfected and mopped bathrooms to keep them sanitary and clean.
- \* Leslie's Home and After Care -6811 Chester Avenue, Philadelphia PA 19142
- \* •Established a safe play environment for the children.
- \* •Organized and engaged in recreational activities such as games and puzzles.
- \* •Dressed infants and toddlers and changed their diapers.
- \* •Communicated openly with children's parents about daily activities and behaviors.
- \* •Made nutritious breakfasts, lunches, dinners and snacks for the children.
- \* •Maintained a child-friendly environment with access to outdoor activities.
- \* •Monitored each student's educational progress with individualized charts and files.
- \* •Administered medications and kept appropriate records.

# **EDUCATION**

## **Diploma**

John Bartram High School - Philadelphia, PA September 2009 to 2012